sqlmaestro.com 2019-12-15

# Database tools for MySQL, SQL Server, PostgreSQL, SQLite, Oracle, DB2, Firebird by SQL Maestro Group

Partners

Testimonials

**Kym Harper :** "Beautifully presented tools (and web site) and great service. I will be sending links to many other individuals who should be interested. Wishing you every continued success and thank you again".

**Stephen Arrowel, Database Administrator:** "We are in the process of implementing Firebird solutions at multiple levels in our international organization. We expect that SQL Maestro Group will do nothing short of revolutionize the way we develop and maintain our Firebird databases. The continuous improvement and development means that the product is extremely flexible and will grow with us. The service and responsiveness of the Support Team has been exceptional. They have devoted countless hours to understanding our needs, so that we could get a Firebird administration tool which would be so simple and effective in use. SQL Maestro Group is helping Sytrax sail into the 21st Century".

Customers

| 

Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and agreed to notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site;
  2. The organization collecting the information;
  3. How the information is used;
  4. With whom the information may be shared;
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under SQL Maestro Group control;
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.  

**Information Collection and Use**  
SQL Maestro Group is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. SQL Maestro Group collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Order**  
We use a third-party provider to process orders. That company requests information from the user on their order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. Some of that information is transferred to us. If we have trouble processing an order, contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Use of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, SQL Maestro Group, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and E-mail address.

**Surveys & Contests**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our user's information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the industry-standard encryption software: SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, as when you are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our user's information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies is added; our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customer's information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

**Site and Service Updates**  
We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via E-mail or phone.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an "opt-out" mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their E-mail address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by sending "[unsubscribe](https://www.sqlmaestro.com/en/news/subscribe/)" form.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an E-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

| 

#### [Christmas Sale](https://www.sqlmaestro.com/purchase/)

---  
  
SQL Maestro Group wish you a **Merry  Christmas!**  
  
We're happy to grant you a [**20% discount**](https://www.sqlmaestro.com/purchase/) for all our products and bundles till **December 31!**  
  
Company news[](https://www.sqlmaestro.com/rss.xml)

Oct 18, 2019

New version comes with PostgreSQL 12 compatibility, introduces support for stored generated columns, using of planner support functions in functions and some other enhancements.

Aug 8, 2019

New version comes with support for PSQL stored functions, external procedures and functions, DDL privileges, new user properties and a number of other Firebird 3 features, updated SSH client equipped with more secure key exchange algorithms, database profile usage statistics and other enhancements.

Apr 18, 2019

New version introduces SQL Anywhere 17 compatibility, colored tabs, new encryption algorithms in data grids, updated BLOB Editor, database profile usage statistics and a lot of other useful things.

Feature of the day

MS SQL Code Factory allows you to represent numeric data from a query result as a diagram with a possibility of customizing its appearance and export the diagram to the following formats: BMP, Windows metafile, PDF, JPEG, PNG and more. 

Using DB2 Code Factory you can view or edit BLOB data in the following ways: hexadecimal dump, plain text, graphical image or HTML page.
